Yeah?
You wanted to see me?
Yes, Oscar, come on in.
Close the door if you would.
Thank you.
Thanks so much
for talking to me.
Yeah, sure.
(SlGHS) l'm going in
for a procedure today.
ls everything okay?
Yeah.
lt's routine. l'm just
a little bit scared.
l'm sure everything
will be fine.
What's the procedure,
if you don't mind my asking?
lt is a colonoscopy.
Okay.
ln your experience,
what should l be expecting
in terms of sensation
or emotions?
ls there anything
l can do to make it more
pleasurable for me,
or for Dr. Chaudry?
(SlGHS) Oh, my God !
My main concern,
should l have
a safe word?
Yeah.
(lNAUDlBLE)
So, Michael,
you think you can
give me a rundown
on the Buffalo
clients by Monday?
Absolutely. You know what?
l'll do you one better.
Sunday. Sunday night.
Okay. l will
get it Monday.
(CHUCKLES)
Hold on, big guy.
l'm going to put it
in the mail Sunday night,
you'll get it Wednesday.
Okay. Jim, you want to
hit the conference room?
Sure.
Hey, good luck.
Oh, right, this thing.
l remember now.
(WHlSPERlNG)
What's this about?
This is just
me and David,
if that's okay.
lt's okay with me.
He's going to
want me in there.
No. lt's okay,
Michael. We got it.
Really?
Yeah.
All right. Do you mind
if l sit this out?
l have so much work to do,
l feel like l'm going
to blow my brains out.
Okay. You got it.
(DOOR SHUTS)
Am l worried that
Jim and David are having
a meeting without me?
No. Because we are
the three amigos.
And once in a while,
one of the amigos
will go off
to the bathroom,
while the other two
have a secret meeting.
Hey, let me
escort you
to your desk.
Okay. lt's just
three or four steps,
but thank you.
Thank you.
You and Jim
are close, huh?
Yeah. l think the pregnancy
really brought us together.
Hey, what do you
think he and David
are talking about?
What do you. . .
Um, l don't know.
MlCHAEL: Well, you said
good luck to Jim
as he walked in.
Did l?
Doesn't sound like me.
Not very superstitious.
(EXHALlNG)
lf you're lying
to me right now,
Pam,
your baby is gonna
come out a liar.
That's how it works.
They inherit things
through the breast milk.
Please don't talk
about my breast milk.
l just don't want
you to lie to me.
l don't want you
to ever lie to me.
Have l ever lied to you?
Yeah.
l just don't
want you to.
DARRYL: l was rushing
to fill an order.
l put the ladder up to grab
a box of three hole
from the top shelf,
next thing l know,
l'm on the ground,
ladder's on top of me.
And that's how you
broke your ankle?
Yes.
Hmm. lnteresting.
How did the ladder
end up on top of you
if you fell off of it?
This doesn't concern you, man.
You need to walk away.
Oh, really?
l'm sorry. l thought
this was a free country.
l didn't know we were
in Communist Sweden.
lf we were
living in Sweden,
l wouldn't have
to worry about this
because we'd have
universal healthcare.
That's not. . . Okay.
Be quiet.
l'm talking about. . .
(SlGHS) Hmm. . .
l will send this
off to corporate.
Make sure you hold on
to your medical bills.
Feel better.
Thanks, T-man. Later.
So long, Darryl.
Feel better.
He's lying.
He has a doctor's note.
From who? Dr. J?
You really need to
investigate this.
People don't just
fall off of ladders.
Guy on my street
fell off a ladder
painting his house.
lt was on the news.
Since when
have you known Darryl
to rush to do anything
other than to come up here
for birthday cake?
"Y'all having
birthday cake?"
(SCOFFS)
That's not
a very good Darryl.
Please!
And how many
foremen do you know
that pull boxes?
lt just doesn't add up.
TOBY: WeII,
we did a little investigation,
and Dwight had a good point.
The Iadder
didn't reach the top shelf.
l don't know if l believe it,
but I am a fan
of the hardboiIed
detective noveI.
"l'll punch you
into mush, see?"
Uh-huh. Well, if he doesn't
like it, you can tell
that s.o.b that he is fired.
Sorry, l'm going
into a meeting right now.
l will. l love you, too. Bye.
Who was that?
Sorry about that.
What'd l miss?
Michael, we would like
to continue the rest of
this meeting in private,
please,
if you don't mind.
l do not mind.
Yes, l do.
No, l don't. Yes, l do.
No, l don't mind.
Catch you guys on
the flippity-flop.
Oh, this. . .
Call waiting. Yeah?
Uh-huh.
Well, you tell the mayor
he just lost six votes.
(DOOR SLAMS SHUT)
They've been
in there a while.
Yeah.
Can't be good.
No.
Think they're
talking about me?
No, l think they're
talking about me.
Yeah. That makes
way more sense.
Okay. Thanks, boss.
MlCHAEL: What is
Jim telling him?
That I can't handle this job?
That's bull crap.
That is bull crap.
Although it has been
chaotic lately.
Corporate shut down
the Buffalo branch,
which left us to absorb
all of their clients.
I will tell you,
there has been
work every day.
Had to come in
on a Saturday
to retrieve. . . l left
my cell phone here.
Hey, Kelly.
(SlGHS) So jealous
of your boobs.
Thank you.
Um, listen,
l just wanted
to confirm
that you're not
coming to the wedding,
which is totally
understandable,
and more than fine.
ls Ryan going?
l don't know,
he hasn't RSVPed yet.
We invited everyone
in the office
to our wedding,
even though
we realized
most people
wouldn't be able
to make the drive
to Niagara Falls.
(WHlSPERlNG) Which is why
we're having it
in Niagara Falls.
Then Michael
told everyone
they could have
Friday and Monday
off if they came.
So now, people have
to decide if they want
to come to our wedding
or have to work.
Here's the deal.
l really want to go.
But l'm not gonna go
if Ryan doesn't go,
because it's kind of
a waste of time.
That came out wrong.
lt would be awesome
if you could try
to get him to go
because l'd really like
to be there to support Jim.
(KEYS CACKLlNG)
What can l do
for you, hoss?
How are your
sales doing?
How are my sales doing?
Busted.
You know, my numbers
are down a little bit.
And it's 'cause
of the economy.
You're not buying it.
You're good.
Okay, the truth is
l have been having
trouble focusing lately.
l'm in this weird,
flirty, nebulous thing
with this cousin of mine.
And it's a total mind f'er.
Again with the cousin.
Oh, l'm sorry, Phyllis.
You explain
this email. Okay?
"Hey, Andy, let's go
visit Grandma and then
get drunk together. Ha, ha."
Shh. l'm just trying to
figure out what's going on
in that room, okay?
MlCHAEL: WaIIace
had to show up
on the one
four-month period that
l'm completely overwhelmed.
You know when they say,
"lt's so crazy
it just might work?"
Well, l don't believe that.
l say go for
the airtight plan.
And that is why
l am having Andy
wheel me into
the conference room
inside a makeshift
cheese cart.
lt is just elegant.
MlCHAEL: Be my eyes.
You got it.
What have we here?
Oh !
STANLEY: Hello.
Just backing up
and turning around.
Hey, we're
gonna do this. . .
(EXCLAlMlNG)
lt's not for you.
(SPEAKlNG FRENCH)
l took the liberty
of preparing for you
a cheese platter,
which l will place here
on the eastern wall
of the conference room.
Cheese platter?
(ANDY SPEAKlNG FRENCH)
From the Wisconsin region,
a nice, firm cheddar.
Also from the great
state of Wisconsin,
an aged Parmesan.
Here you will find
a cheddar-style spread,
which has reacted
nicely with the air
to form a light rind,
which l think you'll find both
challenging and delicious.
At that point, l would
recommend you take
a quick trip
south of the border to
the great state of lllinois,
where you will find
this fine blue
cheese dressing.
lf l may be so bold,
it's a lot of fun
to let the goldfish
take a little swim
in the blue cheese.
(SPEAKlNG FRENCH)
All right, well,
l should go.
Thanks for this.
You've given me
a lot to think about.
Please promise me
you won't do anything
until we speak.
No, l won't.
(SlGHlNG) All right.
Hey, thanks for
taking the time.
Yeah. Appreciate it.
Thank you, Jim.
Erin,
is Michael around?
l think
he's around here.
ls that. . .
Hey, hey, hey.
You must have
walked right past me.
How you doing?
Yeah. Could we talk in
your office for a sec?
Yes, definitely.
Okay.
TOBY: lt sounds
like a EMD P40.
Nah. That's a GE.
The P40 is much
higher-pitched.
You're into trains?
Have been
my whole life.
Wow!
l'm rebuilding
a turn-of-the-century
steam engine
in my slaughterhouse.
That's so cool.
Yeah.
Wow!
l'd love to take
a look at that.
Yeah. lt's just
a run-of-the-mill
slaughterhouse,
but sure, anytime.
Well, you know,
because of the trains.
Wait, someone's coming.
Oh, boy. Oh, boy.
lt's Darryl ! Get down !
He's not using crutches!
Get the camera.
Start taping.
Drive!
Worker's comp, my ass!
l can't believe this.
Hey, you ass (BLEEP) !
Toby!
TOBY: You gonna eat all
that dog food yourself?
No, no!
Oh, man !
You okay?
Just drive.
Hey, Ryan.
Hey.
So, l just wanted to
confirm that you're not
coming to my wedding.
Yeah, l might stop by.
lt costs about
$75 per person.
Okay. l once had
a glass of Cognac
that cost $77, so. . .
Can you just tell me now
if you're coming or not?
Yes. l'm coming
to your wedding.
Okay. Ryan Howard, yes.
Probably yes.
Kelly Kapoor, yes.
Are you sure you're
okay with these new
responsibilities?
Look who you're talking to.
Just trying to figure out
the best way to utilize
everyone's talents.
Well, l would say
that my greatest talent
is being the best
man, woman or child
to have ever run
this branch. Ever.
And what about Jim?
You think Jim is
someone who is ready
to move into
a management position?
Permission to speak
on the record.
Please do.
Jim is like Big Bird.
He is tall and yellow
and very nice.
But would l put him
in charge? No.
l don't think so. He. . .
Big Bird doesn't make
the tough decisions.
lf l was going to put
someone in charge,
l would put Bert in charge.
Or l would put
one of the real
grownups in charge,
like Maria.
Or Gordon, maybe.
l thought you liked Jim.
Very much.
Jim is my best friend.
But here's his
performance report.
Right here.
Now, this was
written by Toby,
who we all know is
extremely reliable.
"Constant office distraction.
Spends way too much
time at reception.
"Antagonizes other salesmen.
Not at all what
he thinks he is."
lt's not very well written.
But you get the gist.
ls there anybody else
you think could run the
day-to-day of the branch?
l could just continue
to run it myself, that's. . .
Jim had an interesting
idea to help you with
this extra workload.
And it involved
you being promoted
to oversee all
northeast sales.
And then Jim
would be promoted
to your position.
This was Jim's idea?
Mmm-hmm.
Wow!
Well, l'd have to talk
to my mother and my guy
at H&R Block.
Okay. But, well, see,
here's the thing, though.
The plan doesn't work
unless we have
someone to replace you.
l was hoping. . .
Plus, we have to
worry about Jim.
He has another job offer.
We may have to replace him.
l didn't tell Michael because
l thought he'd try to help.
Example, he handed out
Jell-O shots at the 23rd mile
of the Steamtown Marathon.
Jim, can you walk me down
to my car for a second?
Sure.
(lNAUDlBLE)
l can't help but feel
partially responsible.
Little pick-me-up.
Those are the best.
Sugar rush.
When you were in
the office earlier
talking to Wallace,
did l come up at all?
Well, we did talk about
how handsome you are.
Why don't we head into
your office and talk?
MlCHAEL:
Okay. What did we. . .
God ! We said. . .
l know
there were certain
things we said.
Michael, look.
l'll just be honest with you.
Earlier today, l spoke with
Wallace about a promotion.
And l actually think
that talk went really well.
Mmm-hmm.
And then,
after he spoke with you,
for some reason,
it felt like
things had changed.
Hmm. That's weird.
That's weird.
Kind of weirding me out.
Did you know that
Lincoln's secretary
was named Kennedy?
Michael,
did you say anything?
(SlGHS) Tell you what,
when you leave this office,
l'm going to call Wallace
and l'm going to tell him
that you should
get that promotion.
Really?
Yes.
You will?
Wanna do it right now?
Yes.
l tried to keep
Michael in the dark.
l should have known
that he can do just as much
damage in the dark.
l need to see
your pupils.
l have to see if
they're dilating. . .
STANLEY: Toby! Dwight!
ls that them?
Definitely.
You come to my house,
bust up my trash cans,
call my baby sister
an ass (BLEEP) and
told her to eat dog food?
We thought that
she was you.
Why would you think
a lady is me?
Are you serious?
Because you look
exactly alike.
Am l the only one?
TOBY: That's too far. . .
Are you getting this?
l mean. . .
l don't see it.
Here's what
l'm gonna do.
l'm calling corporate
and l'm filing a complaint
against both of you.
Oh, Darryl.
Come on, Gwyneth.
Sad.
This is David.
Hey, David,
this is Michael. . .
Michael Scott here.
Yeah.
Just wanted
to talk to you
about Jim Halpert.
l understand
that he did not
receive that promotion,
and l wanted to see
what l could do
to nudge you
in the right
direction.
So, what,
you're changing
your mind about Jim?
Absolutely not!
Like l said before,
Jim is fantastic
and he deserves this job.
Michael, it seems like
you're cutting in and out.
This is not what
you said earlier.
What. . . Here's the thing.
Jim is the best
man for this job.
l think you should
give it to him.
Well, it doesn't change
what you showed me
in Jim's fiIe.
What?
Well. . .
That was an anomaly.
That file had been falsified.
Toby Flenderson
is doing drugs.
Michael, I really
don't know what's
going on down there, but...
(POLlCE SlREN WAlLlNG)
Oh, damn it!
I am getting pulled over
for talking on my cell.
Damn it!
Hey, Darryl, look,
we're here to apologize.
We're cool.
DWlGHT: Wait.
They're using the lift
as their own personal
elevator.
STANLEY: What?
He broke his ankle
climbing over the railing,
then he lied about it
because it was a misuse
of company equipment.
Case closed.
Stupidest thing
l ever heard.
Really?
Then why is there new wood
only on one railing?
Let's just check
the security tapes, Toby.
Well, you know,
l don't think there's
any reason to check them,
but l suppose
if we wanted to be
really certain.
All right. Yeah.
Fine, so whatever.
Yes!
TOBY: You really did it.
Now, l would like
to file an official
complaint to corporate
because Darryl lied
on an official form.
And l'm telling them
you guys sexually
harassed my sister.
(SCOFFS) No judge
is gonna believe that.
Okay.
Look, we could
all file complaints
against each other
and just drown in a sea
of paperwork, but,
you know, we'll just
move on with our lives.
So, Dwight and Darryl
came to an agreement
that they would both file
complaints
with corporate,
and now l get to do
all this paperwork.
We worked it out.
Hey, hey, Jim.
lt would make me feel
really good right now
if you would just
punch me in the face,
all right? Just do it.
How many times
have l asked you
to put me up for
a branch manager job?
l never recommended you
because l didn't
want to lose you.
And l didn't
want to lose Pam.
Now l don't want
to lose the baby.
So, instead,
you screwed me?
That's what she said.
No.
David Wallace
is calling.
We're kind of
in the middle
of something here.
Should l tell him
you'll call back?
Yeah. No.
l'll tell him myself.
Let's both.
Hello?
DAVID: Hey, Michael.
Yes.
You got Jim
there with you?
No, it's just us.
Actually, can you call Jim in?
I want him on this. PIease.
Oh ! Well, here
he is right now.
Come in.
(CLlCKlNG TONGUE)
(lMlTATlNG DOOR SQUEAKlNG)
Hi, David.
Hey, guys.
So, I spoke to AIan.
We had kind of
an unconventional idea,
which I think is pretty cool.
But it only works if
everyone's onboard.
Well, just as long
as it means Jim
becomes a manager.
We were thinking
of having two branch
managers in Scranton.
Both of you guys
working as co-managers.
Jim wouId handIe
the day-to-day,
and Michael, you would
focus on cIients
and big picture stuff.
Wow!
That sounds pretty cool.
l like that!
So, manager
and co-manager.
Co-manager and co-manager.
See, there are a lot
of moving pieces
and this is the only way
I can sell it upstairs.
Well, that might be
a little confusing
for people
because they
know me as manager.
All right, hey, Michael,
can you pick up
for one second?
Okay, Iook, I'm not
going to force you
into anything.
If you're willing
to lose Jim, fine.
You just say so.
We'II find another
soIution. Okay?
Is that what
you want to do?
Okay, people, listen up!
MlCHAEL: Okay, everybody.
BOTH: l have
an announcement
to make.
Fraud was
committed in. . .
Whoa!
Do you have
an announcement?
l was making it.
Everybody,
David Wallace
and l have talked,
and we have decided
to promote Jim to the
position of co-manager.
Co-manager of what?
Of your butt!
And your butt,
and your butt, and your butt.
All of Scranton branch butts.
What's happening
to you, Michael?
What's happening to me?
l am also being
promoted to co-manager.
We will be
co-managers together.
Jim Halpert, welcome.
Thank you.
(YELLlNG)
Niagara Falls in October?
Hells yeah !
Do you think that
you could send in
your RSVP card?
No. l'll just
tell you now. Easier.
Well, you have to
choose a food option,
and there's information
in there about directions
and lodging.
l'll just have
whatever's fanciest,
unless there's ribs,
and l'll just get
all the other information
the day of. l'll text you.
You are going to text me
the morning of my wedding
to ask for directions. . .
Mmm-hmm. Right.
. . .and you will eat
whatever is fanciest?
Unless there's ribs.
Rude.
So rude, right?
Mmm-hmm.
Oh, my gosh.
l have been chasing
people down all day.
lt's incredible.
Pam, my bag was there.